[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What US state enacted Proposition 215, the Compassionate Use Act, which allowed sick and dying patients to legally use marijuana for medicinal purposes?", "correct_answer": "California", "incorrect_answers": ["Alabama", "Hawaii", "Ohio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from the movie Steel Magnolias delivered this memorable line?\nAll gay men have track lightin. And all gay men are named Mark, Rick, or Steve.", "correct_answer": "Clariee", "incorrect_answers": ["Truvy", "Annelle", "MLynn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Carpenter ants have become a problem because of the wood they eat.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What scale is used only to describe hurricanes forming in the Atlantic Ocean and northern Pacific Ocean?", "correct_answer": "Saffir-Simpson Hurricane Scale", "incorrect_answers": ["Hamilton-Norwood scale", "Beaufort scale", "Fujita scale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is special about the red ants of the Southwestern USA and Central and South America?", "correct_answer": "They steal larvae for slaves.", "incorrect_answers": ["They can live in temperatures from 11 degrees Centigrade to 51 degrees Centigrade.", "They can live for six days without food or water.", "They can change color."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2003 movie Underworld, there were 3 main species - humans, vampires, and what other species?", "correct_answer": "Lycans", "incorrect_answers": ["Ulfhednar", "Lycanthropes", "Werewolves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Statistics is useless, since you can design an experiment to statistically prove anything you want to prove.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these represents the largest group of soldiers?", "correct_answer": "Battalion", "incorrect_answers": ["Company", "Squad", "Platoon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Snakes belong to the following category.", "correct_answer": "Reptiles", "incorrect_answers": ["Invertebrates", "Lizards", "Mammals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first human to have an inch long tooth was a fourth grade student in Ontario, Canada.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1989 comedy Bill and Teds Excellent Adventure, what was Bills last name and title?", "correct_answer": "Preston, Esq.", "incorrect_answers": ["Parker, Third Lord of Prescott", "Princeton III", "Peter the Great"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What medical term defines the fear of eating?", "correct_answer": "Phagophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Mastophobia", "Foodophobia", "Emetophobia"]}]